你真的要坐在谢尔顿的宝座上吗
Should you really be sitting in Sheldon's spot?
他人在德州  不可能会知道
He's Texas, he'll never know.
我觉得话别说太早
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
是啊  他的屁屁可敏感了
Yeah, he has a very sensitive butt.
是真的
Well, it's true.
有次他误坐到一堆硬币上  还能感觉出来
Once I saw him sit on a bunch of loose change
总共是多少钱
and add it up.
霍华德有跟你联系吗
Have you heard from Howard?
有啊  他在太空总署的演讲很成功
I did. His talk at NASA went great.
谢尔顿没在台下找茬吗
Sheldon didn't heckle him?
没有  而且他超级乖
No, in fact, he was so well-behaved,
华仔还买了传奇太空人的摇头公仔
Howie bought him a Buzz Aldrin bobble head
跟太空人冰激凌奖励他呢
and astronaut ice cream.
-大伙们  -斯图尔特
- Hey, guys.-  Hey, Stewart!
-大家好吗  -很好
- How's it going? - Good.
谢尔顿不在  我们想干嘛都行
Sheldon's out of town, so we can do whatever we want.
我们还从他不喜欢的那家泰式餐厅叫了外卖
We even ordered from the Thai place he doesn't like.
好吃吗
Oh, how is it?
超难吃  千万别告诉他
Disgusting. Do not tell him.
你们今晚想干嘛
What do you guys want to do tonight?
不知道
I don't know.
我跟华仔说如果今晚没事
Well, I told Howie if I wasn't busy,
我就会去陪他妈妈
I'd spend the night at his mom's.
所以拜托你们赶紧想出事来做吧
so for God's sake, think of something.
斯图尔特  你没事吧
Stuart? Are you okay?
我感觉不太舒...
No, I don't feel so...
-斯图尔特  -斯图尔特
- Oh, Stuart? - Stuart?
天啊  你们快来救他
Oh, my God, you guys need to do something!
-斯图尔特  -我叫救护车
- Stuart? - Calling 911.
-太迟了  -什么叫太迟了
- Well, it's too late. - What do you mean it's too late?
他已经被在座的某人给谋杀了
He's been murdered by someone in this room.
-天啊  -不是吧
- Oh, my God. - Oh, come on!
欢迎来到库萨帕里
Welcome to another classic
又一经典的神秘谋杀夜
Koothrappali murder mystery dinner.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
你不能走
You can't leave.
你也斯图尔特·布鲁姆谋杀案的嫌疑人之一
You're a suspect in the mysterious murder of Stuart Bloom.
我都不知道他姓布鲁姆
I didn't know his last name was Bloom.
是的  他就姓那个
Yeah, it's Bloom.
你真的要躺在地上
Are you really gonna lie on the floor
装一晚上的死人吗
and pretend to be dead all night?
那你觉得我本来要在家做啥
What do you think I was gonna do at home?
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
你又要让我们扮演成一帮口音奇怪
Are you gonna make us pretend to be a bunch of lame characters
角色傻逼的人物吗
with silly accents?
"口音奇怪的傻逼角色..."
"Lame characters with silly ac..."
你算是哪门子的女演员啊
What kind of actress are you?
你说得对  抱歉
You're right, I'm sorry.
-其实听起来挺好玩的  -谢谢
- It... sounds like fun. - Thank you.
这种假惺惺女演员  这烂爆了好吗
That kind of actress. This sucks!
别这样嘛  各位
Come on, guys.
拉杰为这游戏废了不少心思呢
Raj put a lot of effort into this.
这很棒啊
And that's great.
完全不悲催  很棒
It's not sad, it's great.
今晚扮演一下其他人应该会挺好玩的
I think it might be fun to be someone else tonight.
其实今晚大家都是演自己
Actually, you're all just gonna be yourselves.
好吧  如果要玩
All right, if I'm doing this,
姐就要赢  所以先说清楚
I'm playing to win, so just to be clear:
这游戏是指我们其中一人杀死斯图尔特吗
If we're ourselves, that means one of us killed Stuart?
非常好  伯纳黛特
Very good, Bernadette.
你就是个波克西·巴克锡
You are a regular Byomkesh Bakshi.
那是啥  印度版夏洛克·福尔摩斯吗
What is that, like, the Indian Sherlock Holmes?
也可能夏洛克是英国版的波克西·巴克锡
Or is Sherlock Holmes the English Byomkesh Bakshi?
根据维基百科  是先有夏洛克
According to Wikipedia, Sherlock Holmes came first.
很好  大家都是波克西·巴克锡
Great, everyone's a Byomkesh Bakshi.
现在发给各位
Now... here are some
关于你们自己的秘密资料
secret facts about each of you,
包含你们自己是不是凶手
including whether you are the murderer.
游戏过程中  随时都可以问对方
Throughout the game, feel free to ask
各种问题来得到线索
each other questions to uncover clues.
懂了
Got it. Hey...
谁是凶手啊
who's the murderer?
像这种问题不能问
Any question but that.
抱歉
Sorry. Hey...
谁不是凶手啊
who's not the murderer?
伯纳黛特  能别站得离我这么近吗
Bernadette, can you not stand so close to me?
有什么关系  你都死了
What do you care? You're dead.
随你高兴
Suit yourself.
但我貌似能看见你裙里风光
But I can kind of... see up your skirt.
谢谢你送我摇头公仔
Thank you for my bobble head.
也谢谢你没在我演讲时找我茬
Thank you for not making fun of me during my speech.
忍住不找茬很不容易吧  巴兹
It wasn't easy. Was it Buzz?
我们不能两手空空的去你妈妈家吧
We can't show up to your mom's empty-handed.
应该带点礼物
We should bring something.
我已经带了
I already am.
我带了知识的馈赠
I'm bringing the gift of knowledge.
天啊
Oh, boy.
无论她的圣经写过啥
Despite what her Bible says,
最新的考古研究显示
recent archeological studies indicate that
虽然旧约圣经中曾提到过骆驼
although camels are referenced in the Old Testament,
但骆驼实际出现在中东的时间
they didn't exist in the Middle East
比圣经里晚了几百年
until hundreds of years later.
我本来是要说带个蛋糕或者派去
I was gonna say we pick up a cake or a pie.
但羞辱她的信仰也很有心意
But an insult to her faith is always thoughtful.
接下来呢
So, what happens next?
我不能直接说出来
I can't tell you that.
但凶手很可能
But perhaps the killer dropped
在公寓里留下了一道
a fun and imaginative clue
有趣又创意十足的线索哦
somewhere in the apartment.
我要去检查一下冰箱
Ooh, I'm gonna check the fridge,
看看啤酒里有没有藏什么线索
and see if there are any clues inside a beer.
我找到了个东西
Hey, I-I found something.
看起来像一个拿着行李箱的小人偶
It looks like a little man with a briefcase.
他是克莱伦斯·戴罗
Oh, no, no. That's Clarence Darrow.
是谢尔顿发明的律师版蛇棋中的角色
It's from a game Sheldon made up called Chutes and Lawyers.
滑道让你倒退  前进则是
You slide down a chute and then work your way back up
靠上诉系统慢慢爬
through the appellate system.
跟那不同的是  我的游戏好玩多了
Well, unlike that, my games are much more fun.
我能问你个问题吗
Okay, can I ask you something?
你为什么总喜欢找我们玩这些游戏
Why do you like making us do this stuff?
可能跟我小时后在印度时是个胖子有关
Well, I guess it goes back to when I was a fat kid in India,
那时候我都没有朋友
and didn't have any friends.
我不知道你以前是个胖子
I didn't know you were fat.
是啊  我...
Yeah, I was...
我念中学的时候体重有90公斤呢
I was 200 pounds by the time I was in middle school.
老被别的孩子欺负
Kids were mean.
虽然在印度牛是神圣的动物
Cows may be sacred there,
可是你身形像牛却一点都不好
but it doesn't help if you look like one.
总之那时的我很孤独
Anyway, I was pretty lonely,
只好自己编故事和游戏娱乐自己
so I had to make up my own stories and games,
我暗自发誓
and I promised myself
如果我有了朋友
if I ever made any friends that...
我一定会跟他们一起玩这些游戏
that I would play those games with them.
真是让人又怜又爱
That is so sweet.
我见过你以前的照片
I've seen old pictures of you.
你一点都不胖啊
You were never a fat kid.
是的  我跟羚羊一样苗条
No, I was svelte as a gazelle.
我是一只拥有讲故事天赋的羚羊
A gazelle blessed with a flair for storytelling.
这个呢  这貌似是一张收据
Hey, what about this? It looks like a receipt.
什么收据
What's it for?
买咖啡的
For a cup of coffee.
但上面的日期是20年后
But it's dated 20 years from now.
来自未来的收据
From the future?!
真是有趣又创意十足
How fun and imaginative.
所以我们中有一个人从未来回来
So one of us came back from the future
-杀死了斯图尔特  -没错
- to murder Stuart? - Correct.
那只拥有讲故事天赋的羚羊
Does the gazelle with a flair for storytelling
知道他的故事是在抄袭《终结者》吗
know he's just ripping off Terminator?
那个自以为是的家伙知道《终结者》
Does the smart-ass know that Terminator was actually
卡梅隆后来承认《终结者》是受到60年代电视科幻剧《外星界限》
里面的两集故事《士兵》和《玻璃手的魔鬼》的启发而创作
其实是抄袭哈兰·埃里森为《外星界限》
ripped off from an Outer Limits script called
编写的一集名为"玻璃手的魔鬼"的剧本吗
Demon With a Glass Hand, by Harlan Ellison?
那只羚羊知道哈兰·埃里森后来又说
Oh, does the gazelle know that according to Harlan Ellison,
《终结者》不是抄袭《玻璃手的魔鬼》
it was not ripped off from Demon With a Glass Hand,
而是抄袭他为《外星界限》编写的另外一个剧本
but was ripped off from another Outer Limits script he wrote
名为《士兵》吗
called The Soldier?
我要再来一瓶"线索"
I'm gonna need another clue.
好
Okay...
把花和派给我
give me the flowers and pie.
但如果我们敲门  礼物在你手里
But if we show up and you're holding them,
她会认为这些都是你买的
she'll think they're only from you.
本来就是我买的
They are only from me.
你说自己就是最好的礼物
You said the gift of you was enough.
话是这么说  但现在我手里拿着花和派
Yes... but now that I've seen what the gift of me
显得我这份礼更大了
with flowers and pie looks like,
所以你休想拿回去了
there's no going back.
我已经等不及想看她一脸惊喜的样子
Boy, I can't wait to see the look on her face...
我们现在就走
We're leaving right now.
-怎么了  -没事
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
谢尔顿  告诉我发生什么事了
What? Sheldon, tell me what's going on!
我看见我妈跟一个裸男纠缠在一起
I saw my mommy with a naked man
她想再次"当妈妈"
and she was trying to be a mommy again.
你想谈一谈吗
You ready to talk about it?
我还不够醉呢
I'm not nearly drunk enough.
够醉了
Okay.
你知道看见自己妈妈在蹂躏别人
Do you have any idea what it's like to see
是什么感觉吗
your mother ravaging someone?
蹂躏鸡胸肉算吗
Does a brisket count?
抱歉  兄弟  的确难以忍受
I'm sorry, buddy, that's rough.
她不是知道我们会来吗
But didn't she know we were coming?
不知道
No.
我想给她一个惊喜
I wanted to surprise her.
经历这种事之后  我该跟她说什么呀
What am I supposed to say to her after something like this?
-她有从窗户看见你吗  -没有
- Well, did she see you in the window? - No.
那就什么都别说
Then don't say anything.
我一定要说
I have to.
如果我们想拥有一段健康的母子关系
How can we ever hope to have a healthy relationship
我就得告诉她我对她有多失望
if I don't tell her how disappointed I am,
而且我这辈子都不会原谅她
and that I'll never forgive her?
那也别用手机说啊
Well, don't do it on the phone.
不是啦  我只是告诉她我要去找她
No, I'm just going to tell her I'm coming
这样她才赶紧会把那个爽歪歪的人打发走
so she can give that Good Time Charlie the heave-ho.
这是一场艰难的对话
That's some tough talk.
我就不跟你过去了
I may need to cut you off.
你最好跟我过去
Yeah, maybe you better.
我可是喝了一大口酒
I took a pretty big sip.
你妈是个成年人了
Look, she's a grown woman.
你爸又不在这么久了
And-and your dad's been gone a long time.
或许你真不应该多管闲事
Maybe this is none of your business.
恕难同意
I beg to differ.
我曾经住在那个生殖器里
I used to live in those genitals.
如果有人想搬进我的"旧房间"
And if someone wants to move into my old room,
那我至少有投票的权利吧
I should at least get a vote.
各位嫌疑犯
Okay, murder suspects,
莱纳德发现了凶手使用过的时光机
Leonard has found the time machine the killer must've used.
大家都坐进去
You're all inside it,
现在我们要穿越时空啦
and we hurtle through the very fabric of time.
欢迎来到20年后的未来
And welcome to 20 years in the future.
喂  你们刚刚穿越时空
Hey, you guys just time-traveled.
别看起来这么没劲好吗
Stop looking so bored.
我的啤酒还有气泡  我的奶子没有下垂
Well, my beer isn't flat and my rack's not saggy.
所以目前为止  未来还不错
So far, the future's great.
我可以去厕所吗
Hey, can I go to the bathroom?
去吧  别看起来太生气勃勃
Fine, just try not to look too alive.
这我可是专家
That's my jam.
我们其中一人回到过去杀死斯图尔特
So one of us went back in time to kill Stuart?
为什么
But why?
或许这个能回答你们的疑问
Perhaps this will help.
这是关于未来的
Here are some facts
你们的一些事情
about yourselves in the future
里面可能包含线索哦
that might contain a clue.
我获得了诺贝尔生理学奖
Hey, I-I won the Nobel Prize in physiology.
然后我用奖金把斯图尔特的漫画店买下来
Then I used the money to buy Stuart's comic book store,
关了那店  好让谢尔顿多放注意力在我身上
and close it down so Sheldon would pay attention to me.
这主意还不赖
Not the worst idea.
我是一名住在伦敦的著名演员
Hey, I'm a famous actress living in London.
我是斯坦福大学的教授
I'm a professor at Stanford.
看来你们就算远距离也能很相爱
So I guess you two are making it work long distance.
错
Oh, no.
在这次游戏中  因为你们各自职业的有了起色
In this game, as your careers both took off,
所以分道扬镳了
you drifted apart.
有点像未来的我
Kind of like how future me
在成为年老色衰却柔软依旧的麦当娜的
lost touch with you guys after I became boy toy
小男宠后就跟你们断了联系了
for the wrinkled, but still flexible, Madonna.
你的卡上说什么  伯纳黛特
What does your card say, Bernadette?
等一下
Eh, eh, eh, hang on.
你觉得如果我俩都事业有成的话
Do-do you think we'd really drift apart
就真的会分手吗
if we both became successful?
当然不会
Of course not.
如果我成了大明星  要搬去别的地方
If I became a famous actress and had to move,
你当然跟着我走啦
you would just come with me.
但如果我有机会成为终身教授
But if I get a chance to be a tenured professor,
我就没法随便决定去留了
I might not have that much choice in where I end up.
没错  但如果我成名了
Yeah, but if I become a successful actress,
我们都不用为钱操心了
we wouldn't need the money.
研究科学可不是为了钱
Well, you don't go into science for the money.
只有你这么想吧
Speak for yourself.
上个月  我的公司同时发现
Last month, my company both invented
和治愈了多动眼综合征
and cured Restless Eye Syndrome.
财源滚滚啊  爱眨眼的呆瓜们
Ka-ching, ya blinky chumps.
所以  如果我的事业要我去别处发展
So, wait, if my career took me somewhere else,
你也许不会跟我走
you might not go?
是他先开始的
He started it.
好了  各位  新的背景设定
Okay, okay, guys-- new back stories.
佩妮和莱纳德  你们小俩口
Uh, Penny and Leonard, you two lovebirds are
已经功成名就  双宿双飞在纽约了
super successful and living in New York.
你是著名演员  你是著名教授
Uh, you're an actress, you're a professor
膝下围绕着三个漂亮宝贝
and you have three beautiful kids.
太好了
Great.
什么  你觉得我会让如此完美的身材
Really? You think I'm putting
生出三个小孩来吗
this body through three kids?
好  我们开始吧
Okay, let's do this.
祝你好运
Good luck.
你...
You...
你不跟我一起来吗
Aren't you gonna come with me?
站在旁边听你和你妈讨论她的性生活吗
While you confront your mother about her sex life?
我宁愿穿着露臀皮裤回去刚才的酒吧
I'd rather go back to that bar in ass-less chaps.
妈妈
Mother?
Mother.
妈妈
Mother?
谢利  真高兴你回家了
Shelly! I'm so glad you're here!
我看到你光着身子做爱了
I saw you having naked sex.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
早些时候  我想回家给你个惊喜
Earlier, I came here to surprise you.
结果透过窗子  我看到你和一个男人纠缠在一起
I looked in the window and I saw you with a man.
谢利  对不起
Oh, Shelly, I'm so sorry.
先进来吧
Come in.
也许我们应该坐下来
Maybe we should sit down
好好聊一聊这事
and talk about this.
能帮我挑个没被你们玷污过的地方吗
Can you recommend a surface you haven't had coitus on?
这话一点不好笑
That's not funny.
我们还是坐餐桌边上聊吧
Maybe we should sit at the table.
我想你一定
Well, I'm sure that, uh,
有很多...
you...
问题想问
have a lot of questions.
那个男人是谁
Who was he?
他名叫罗恩
His name is Ron.
我和他是在祈祷小组认识的
I met him at my prayer group.
你们之间开始多久了
How long have you been involved with him?
几个月
A few months.
那在这几个月中
And of those few months,
你变身这种欲乱狂魔已经多久了
how long have you been a demented sex pervert?
你不能这样对你妈妈说话
That is no way to speak to your mother.
对妈妈或许不能
Perhaps not.
可对一个从小到大
But it is a way to speak to a woman
对我念叨圣经  转身却又亵渎了
who quoted the Bible to me my whole life,
一张上等沙发的女人来说就可以
and then desecrates one of Ethan Allen's finest sofas.
我给你一次机会  年轻人
I will give you one opportunity, young man,
赶快道歉
to apologize.
不然呢
Or what?
不然我就罚你回去房间
Or I will send you to your room.
你太荒唐了
That's ridiculous.
我已经是成年人了
I am a grown man.
我是专业的科学家
I am a professional scientist.
而我此时正站在道德的制高点上
And I currently occupy the moral high ground.
回你的房间去
Go to your room.
可人家站在道德的制高点呢
But I occupy the moral high ground.
回你的房间去
Go to your room.
可人家是专业的科学家呢
But I'm a professional scientist.
滚...回你的房间去
Go... to your room!
人家是成年人哦
I'm a grown man.
我们继续玩游戏好吗
Can we please get back to the game?
等...等一下
I-I-In a minute.
我不懂为什么你演艺事业的成功
I-I-I don't understand why any success you have in acting
要比我在科学领域的成就重要得多
is more important than any I have in science.
好吧  如果你在科学上取得了成果
Okay, if you do something cool in science,
你也许会改变整个世界
you might change the world.
如果我成了著名演员
If I become a famous actress...
我才不会告诉你当电影明星爽在哪里呢
I'm not gonna tell you why movie stars are the best.
反正爽就对了
They just are.
真奇怪  你们竟然没讨论过这种事
I'm surprised you guys never talked about this stuff.
难道你和谢尔顿把话都说清楚了吗
Like you and Sheldon have everything figured out?
事实上  我们的恋爱协议里
Actually, our relationship agreement
囊括了各种情况
covers a wide array of scenarios,
包括工作变迁  财务变化
including career changes, financial instability,
智能狗的暴动
intelligent dog uprising...
随带一提  我们准备彻底出卖人类
FYI, we plan on selling out the human race hard.
谁能猜到二十年后我们会变成什么样呢
In 20 years, who knows what'll happen with any of us?
我觉得你和莱纳德会终成眷属
I think you and Leonard will be together.
-真的吗  -真的
- You do? - Yeah.
我觉得你俩是我见过最般配的一对
I think you're the best couple I know.
你人真好
That's so sweet.
-你说什么  -有没有搞错
- What the hell?! - Excuse me?
别闹
Ah-da-da-da-da!
让这位"死者"先说完
Let the dead man talk.
你为什么这么想呢
So, why do you think that?
我觉得你俩提升了彼此的境界
Uh, well, I feel like you guys make each other better.
佩妮让莱纳德走出了宅男世界
Penny brought Leonard out of his shell.
而莱纳德又让
And it seems like Leonard makes Penny
佩妮对世界有了更深层的认识
think more deeply about the world.
我也说不清
I don't know.
你们在一起  互补成为了一个非常棒的人
Together, you two kind of make one awesome person.
斯图尔特
Aw, Stuart.
现在我真为杀了你感到内疚
Now I feel bad for murdering you.
你不是吧
Oh, come on!
佩妮杀的  我赢了
Penny did it! I win!
认输吧  混蛋们
Suck it, jackasses!
我可以进来吗
Hey, can I come in?
显然任何男人都可以乱入这个家
Apparently any man is welcome in this house.
你为何不行
Why not you?
你不是在车上等着吗
I thought you were waiting in the car.
那是一个小时前了  谢尔顿
That was an hour ago, Sheldon.
在德州  一个犹太人坐在房子前面这么久
A Jew sits in front of a house in Texas that long,
"房屋待售"牌就得挂起来了[多是房中介]
"For Sale" signs start to go up.
看来你和你妈妈谈得不顺利
I take it things didn't go smoothly with your mom.
不
No.
我不知道我们该如何度过这个难关
I'm not sure how we're going to get past this.
其实  我...
You know, I...
我自己也曾经经历过
I sort of went through something
这种事情
like this myself.
霍华德  我们都见过你母亲的裸体
Howard, we've all seen your mother naked.
那个女人需要学会系紧睡袍
That woman needs to learn how to tie a robe.
我说的是  我爸离开几年后
I'm talking about when my mom started seeing someone
我妈开始约会
a couple years after my dad left.
我不知道她曾经约会过
I didn't know she did.
她和一个男的约会
Yeah, she was dating this guy,
我对她的态度挺混蛋的
and I was kind of a jerk to her about it.
你做了什么
What did you do?
这样说吧  那是圣殿寺历史上
Well, let's just say it was the most vicious
最恶毒的成人礼演讲
bar mitzvah speech in the history of Temple Beth El.
总之  她和他分手了
Anyway, she broke up with him.
自那以后  她基本上就一直孤身一人
And she's basically been alone ever since.
她从未说过  但我一直觉得
She never said it, but I always felt
我是让她孤单的原因
I was the reason why.
真遗憾
I'm sorry.
不过  基于你的故事
Although, based on your story,
你绝对是让她孤单的原因
you absolutely were the reason why.
我想说的是  你还是不要
All I'm saying is you might not want
阻碍你母亲的幸福比较好
to get in the way of your mom's happiness.
你说的有道理
You may have a point.
我爱我母亲
I love my mother.
哪怕她像个恶魔黄鼠狼般疯狂交配
Even if she fornicates like a demonic weasel.
伤痛已经开始治愈了
And the healing begins.
-你好  -你好
- Hello. - Hello.
你能像成年人一样冷静地讨论这件事了吗
Are you ready to discuss this calmly, like adults?
能
I am.
谢利  很抱歉让你看到那一幕
Shelly, I'm sorry that you saw what you saw.
我知道这让你难以接受
I know that this is hard for you.
母亲  我想最让我生气的
I think what most upsets me about it, Mother,
是你的虚伪
is the hypocrisy.
这与你毕生信奉的
Doesn't this contradict
所有宗教教条  不是相抵触的吗
all the religious rules you've been espousing your whole life?
你说得对  的确抵触  关于这点
You're right, it does, and it's something
我已经挣扎了一段时间
that I'm struggling with these days.
那你为什么还要这样做
Then why are you doing it?
因为我并不完美  谢利
Because I'm not perfect, Shelly.
但那个男人的屁屁很完美
And that man's booty is.
这是对我来说很困惑
Well, this is confusing for me.
但我不想阻碍你幸福
But I don't want to stand in the way of your happiness.
所以
So...
我会在内心谴责你
I'll condemn you internally
但外表保持接受的态度
while maintaining an outward appearance of acceptance.
多谢你基督徒般的宽容
That is very Christian of you.
母亲  如果你准备照这样生活下去
Mother, if you're going to conduct your life in this fashion,
我应该让你知道  世界已经不是
then I should let you know that the world has changed
你年轻时那个样子了
since you were a young woman.
没有短袜舞会[50年代流行]
You know, it's not all sock hops,
冷饮销售员[40年代流行]和种族隔离了
soda jerks and segregation anymore.
你觉得我到底多大年纪了
How old do you think I am?
我要说的是  你得小心
My point is that you're going to need to be careful.
以前保护你的
You used to be protected
是启蒙运动前的神话学
by your pre-enlightenment mythology,
现在你需要一个更强大的朋友
but now you're going to need a stronger friend
叫做安全套
named latex.
你是在对我进行家长性爱教育吗
Are you having the sex talk with me?
一定得有人说啊
Well, someone has to.
-我的上帝啊  -好了
- Oh, dear Lord! - Yeah, well...
别看他  他现在正生你的气呢
No, don't look to Him. He's mad at you right now.
拜托  别撅嘴了
Oh, come on, don't pout.
抱歉我毁了你的游戏
I'm sorry I ruined your game.
我没有撅嘴  我在沉思
I'm not pouting, I'm brooding.
这是性感男人撅嘴的方式
Which is how sexy men pout.
其实挺有趣的
It actually was kind of fun.
你只是假客套而已
You're just saying that.
是的
Yeah.
我喜欢穿越时空的元素
I liked the time travel element.
谢谢  我觉得很有启发性
Thank you. I thought it was inspired.
没错  是受了《终结者》的启发
It was. By Terminator.
我希望二十年后
Well, I hope 20 years from now,
我们还能在一起
we really are all still together
依然是朋友
and still friends.
-肯定是  -当然了
- Definitely. - Of course.
这样吧
Well, hey, how about this?
无论我们到时是不是朋友
Whether we're friends, not friends,
分散在世界各地  无论怎样
scattered around the world, no matter what,
我们说好了  二十年后这天的晚上八点
let's all promise to meet in front of this building
我们在这栋楼前见
exactly 20 years from tonight at 8:00 P.M.
然后像现在一样聚在一起吃晚餐
and have dinner like we always do.
这主意太好了
I love it.
现在就记在手机里
Putting it in my phone right now.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
我的手机没有日历
My phone doesn't have a calendar.
没事  我写在手上
It's all right, I'll just write it on my hand.
搞定
And it's done.
是  说定了
Yup, we're all in.
好的  咱们二十年后见
All right, I'll see you guys in 20 years.
我就知道
I knew it.